import { Topic } from '.'

export const reasoningSet2: Topic = {
    topic: 'Reasoning',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 20,
    totalScore: 200,
    totalTime: 1260,
    questions: [
      {
        question: `Which number completes the series: 11, 22, 44, ?`,
        choices: ['66', '55', '77', '88'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['88'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `If in a code, TAP = UBQ, then TOP = ?`,
        choices: ['UPQ', 'UOQ', 'UQP', 'UQQ'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['UQQ'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which figure is different from the others: Circle, Cylinder, Cube, Cone`,
        choices: ['Circle', 'Cylinder', 'Cube', 'Cone'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Circle'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Find the odd one: Jump, Run, Sit, Dance`,
        choices: ['Jump', 'Run', 'Dance', 'Sit'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Sit'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which one is not a mode of transport?`,
        choices: ['Car', 'Bus', 'Bike', 'Plate'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Plate'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `If A = 1, B = 2, then Z = ?`,
        choices: ['24', '25', '26', '27'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['26'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `What comes next: 1, 4, 10, 19, ?`,
        choices: ['25', '30', '31', '33'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['31'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Rearrange: 'playing / children / are / the / park / in'`,
        choices: [
          'The park children are playing in',
          'Children are playing the park in',
          'The children are playing in the park',
          'In the park are children playing',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['The children are playing in the park'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which pair is different: Pen-Ink, Brush-Paint, Knife-Cut, Pencil-Eraser`,
        choices: ['Pen-Ink', 'Brush-Paint', 'Knife-Cut', 'Pencil-Eraser'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Pencil-Eraser'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Find the odd one out: January, February, March, Sunday`,
        choices: ['January', 'February', 'March', 'Sunday'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Sunday'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which one does not belong to the group: Cow, Goat, Horse, Tomato`,
        choices: ['Cow', 'Goat', 'Horse', 'Tomato'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Tomato'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which word is different: Sad, Angry, Happy, Chair`,
        choices: ['Sad', 'Angry', 'Chair', 'Happy'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Chair'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which is the odd one: Blue, Red, Tall, Yellow`,
        choices: ['Blue', 'Red', 'Tall', 'Yellow'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Tall'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Choose the odd one: 10, 20, 30, 33, 40`,
        choices: ['10', '20', '30', '33'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['33'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `What comes next: 100, 90, 81, ?`,
        choices: ['72', '70', '73', '74'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['72'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which number fits the pattern: 2, 6, 12, 20, ?`,
        choices: ['28', '30', '32', '36'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['30'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Find the mirror image of 'R'`,
        choices: ['Reversed R', 'P', 'B', 'None'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Reversed R'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Choose the pair that has the same relationship: Book-Reading`,
        choices: [
          'Pen-Writing',
          'Knife-Drawing',
          'Cup-Cooking',
          'Shirt-Eating',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Pen-Writing'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `If MONDAY = 123456, what is DAY?`,
        choices: ['456', '321', '654', '345'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['456'],
        score: 10,
       
      },
      {
        question: `Which does not belong: Bat, Ball, Stump, Mirror`,
        choices: ['Bat', 'Ball', 'Stump', 'Mirror'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswers: ['Mirror'],
        score: 10,
       
      }
    ],
  }
  